What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?
Aura
Legend
Brother
Friends
What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?
Timing and Subtitles brought by The Perfect Secretaries Team @ Viki
Yumyung Group's vice chairman, Lee Yeong Joon.
After becoming vice chairman, he's increased the group's profits by more than twice the previous amount.
Because of that he was selected as the number one and most successful, among the youngest CEOs.
When it comes to a great body, face, or how well his suits fit. Ah, he's got everything.
- But, rumors have it that he won't let a single woman touch him.
- That's right.
That doesn't make sense. I've actually been meeting up with him recently.
Of course, he doesn't let me touch him.
- Oppa!
- Vice Chairman!
Why did she do that?
What?
Why did Secretary Kim do that?
Why is she like that?
What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?
- Episode 1 -
Today I've prepared a monotone tie that suits an intellectual and modern-looking image.
- It looks okay.
- Thank you.
Isn't it bright?
The sunlight?
No...
The aura emanating from me.
Yes, it is blinding. Here is the schedule for today.
It's Executive Kim. Should I answer it?
No, he will for sure say that the contract in Vietnam didn't go well.
I don't want to listen to a sinner and ruin my mood from the morning.
A sinner?
Harming others or stealing are not only sins.
Incompetence, but also being ignorant of his incompetence is also a sin.
- Secretary Kim, do you perhaps know?
- What?
- How can a person be incompetent?
- I know, right?
Trying and achieving, it's simple. Why can't they do that?
All people are not like you, Vice Chairman.
- Really?
- Of course.
In my entire life, I have not seen someone as perfect as you, Vice Chairman.
Who is it?
This time, it's someone who's committed a grave sin.
How should I take care of it?
We've arrived.
Vice Chairman! It's a misunderstanding. Misunderstanding.
During working hours, does it make sense that you're going out to get sexual services?
- As an executive director, are you not thinking of our company image?
- I'm sorry.
'M' Group Executive Was Caught Receiving Sexual Services During Working Hours
- Secretary Kim!
- Yes.
- Next schedule.
There's an executive meeting in the new building.
You know it's prohibited to smoke indoors.
Vice Chairman, Vice Chairman, Vice Chairman!
Vice C— Vice Chairman.
Executive Director Jo, don't be too upset.
With the cancellation of the project and now the sexual service article,
Vice Chairman had a lot of expectations and was let down, so he's upset like that.
To be honest, trying to stop the name of our company from spreading through this article
was especially hard for the vice chairman.
Secretary Kim, why did I do that?
I must have been possessed by something. (meaning I was out of my mind)
Don't forget how you're reflecting now, so you can live better from now on.
How about leaving early today and getting some rest?
Should I?
I will be more careful starting tomorrow.
Secretary Im, I'm going to get off work first.
Excuse me, does this mean that he can keeping working still?
Take care of all of Executive Director Jo's desk and possessions immediately.
Have you ever seen the vice chairman give second chances?
After acquiring a global airline which is ranked third in Korean business industries,
within 5 years, the goal is to prompt it to be the number one business nationally and to make it rank in the top ten businesses globally.
After it is announced that we'll be acquiring the global airline business, in order to get it moving
we'll be actively seeking relations and taking orders from America, Indonesia, and Vietnam.
If you look at the business plan for the current financial situation,
since the liquid assets are at 2.24 trillion won and the current liabilities are 0.94 trillion won,
the current liability ratio will be huge around 275 percent.
215.319149.
- Yes?
- If the liquid assets are at 2.24 trillion won,
and if the current liabilities are 0.94 trillion won,
shouldn't the current liability ratio be 215.319149 percent, President Park?
You're right, you're right. I wonder why the numbers are--
Go ahead with the acquisition.
Let's end the meeting.
Oh, it's too war-like in here.
Isn't the Vice Chairman being too much?
My lifespan is shortening. How can I live on being this scared?
Oh, Vice Chairman!
It's not.
I agree with you, too.
Ah, I was so surprised. Since it's his friend, he doesn't want us to curse him, right?
He's been invited to a private party at the Spanish embassy.
Would it be okay if I called you back tomorrow, to reschedule?
- You've improved a lot.
- What?
Your English.
Just 9 years ago when we first went to America, you found it hard to interact with foreigners.
I was like that. It's all thanks to you, Vice Chairman.
You're right, my endless advice to you should have helped you quite a bit.
More than anything, when I had issues with my pronunciation or accents, you weren't hesitant to shame or reprimand me.
That stimulated me a lot.
Shame and reprimand, you say?
Alright, if those help you improve, I'll keep doing the same.
- Thank you.
- But you know,
- you messed up earlier again.
- What?
It's not awc-cent, it's ack-cent.
I learned something again.
I apologize. It's because I have to wear a dress today.
I wasn't able to provide refreshments for you today because of the scheduled meeting. Are you okay?
I don't feel anything. You should know I get like this when I focus.
When I'm like this, I can't even feel hunger.
I'll prepare the refreshments.
This is the newly appointed Spanish ambassador.
Hello. Congratulations on your new position. (In Spanish)
I heard a lot about Vice Chairman Lee Yeong Joon even in Spain.
I look forward to your kind cooperation.
For the past four years, Yumyung Group has ranked first nationally for having a good business image, according to the consumer report.
The Bio Business has recently been approved by the US FDA. ( In English)
We were successful in achieving a trade surplus. (In French)
Working with China, knowing that they have a remarkable network of people. ( In Chinese)
We are planning a diverse array of businesses. (  In German)
- He's so cool.
- Isn't he handsome?
- Oh, he is cool.
- Right, right?
Look at his nose bridge!
He's really-- So, good-looking.
Our eyes met.
One second.
- He's coming this way.
- Does that make sense?
He's coming for me.
What? He's just passing by?
- Leaving me?
- Mirror.
No way.
The ambassador is waiting for you.
Secretary Kim.
Yes?
How do I look right now?
Perfect.
Let's go.
When did you learn Spanish?
What do you mean, Spanish?
You were speaking earlier with the Spanish guys that were trying to pick you up, for quite some time.
Oh that!
I barely picked up English and Chinese, thanks to you.
Where do you think I found the time to learn Spanish? I just got by with my sensibility.
- Sensibility?
- Yes.
If they hand me champagne and look towards me, they probably meant, "excuse me for a moment."
When they look over at you and start speaking, they're all probably compliments,
- so I'd smile and nod my head in agreement.
- Of course.
And when it looks like they're trying to pick me up, I touch my earring with my left hand.
Why is it your left hand?
If I show them my ring, it all gets taken care of.
This is the prize I earned at the last athletic competition.
Amazing.
After living for this long, I guess there does come a day when I'm complimented by you, Vice Chairman.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Anyway, you did well today. When it comes to purses or clothes that you want, let me know.
Rewards will encourage you even more.
Vice Chairman.
I'll refuse your rejection.
That's not it. I have something to say to you.
Don't confess to me. We're in a working relationship.
I wasn't thinking of doing that.
What do you want to say?
Vice Chairman, you should look for a new secretary.
I will now stop working.
Why, all of a sudden?
Just because, for personal reasons.
Then, do as you please.
Why can't I go to sleep?
Why are you all over the place again?
I have an incredible piece of news for you all.
What kind of incredible piece of news? You probably just heard some meaningless rumor.
My dear, this time. It's real.
Alright, those of you who can take it, gather here.
- Hurry and come here.
- I can't handle! I can't!
You know Secretary Kim?
What about Secretary Kim?
Secretary Kim
will resign, I heard.
What? You guys don't believe me?
Of course we don't. Why would Secretary Kim stop working?
She's receiving all the vice chairman's admiration. Why would she quit despite all that's going for her? That doesn't make sense.
It does make sense. I am really quitting.
Really?
Secretary Kim you really stopped working?
Yes, that's how it turned out.
Look, look, I was right. But wasn't it so sudden?
Why? Are you getting married? Are you getting an organ transplanted? Or studying abroad?
It's not any of those.
Then, is it because of the vice chairman's temperament?
It's also not that.
Then why?
Just because of personal reasons.
Vice Chairman is coming in.
Hello.
Hey, is it?
Should we go to her?
I never imagined that Secretary Kim would not be besides the Vice Chairman.
It doesn't feel real to me either.
I will miss you, Secretary Kim.
Then, normally around this time you should be preparing to bring him snacks.
The Darjeeling tea should always be served in this tea set.
The cookies should be from 'H' hotel and placed in threes.
Yes, well.
Why are you asking her that?
Why would I be asking? When Secretary Kim leaves, it's what I'll be doing.
Why is that?
If you look at Secretary Kim, it looks like the vice chairman has high standards when it comes to his secretary's looks.
When Secretary Kim leaves, the only person who could take her place is me.
Ah, these are moments when I'm so jealous of you.
I wish I looked normal like you too.
Since the vice chairman arrives at 7, that means I'll have to be here by 6:30.
I won't be able to sleep. What should I do?
Anyway, what should I do?
Hello.
Changing the swiveling chair, right?
- You're amazing.
- I know what's going on in your mind too.
You are not serious about quitting, are you?
This time, you're wrong.
What could possibly be the reason?
Is it because I made you work at night-time and on the weekends from last month?
I'll post a hiring notice during morning hours.
I'll narrow them down as much as possible, so all you'll have to do is attending the final interview.
You can take care of it.
Employment Eligibility and Requirements
It is sent.
Vice Chairman, do you need anything?
I'll be going to President Park's office now, reschedule the conference call to the afternoon.
Yes.
I'll be eating at my own house, so you should eat accordingly.
Alright.
Secretary Kim! Secretary Kim!
You haven't eaten lunch yet, right? You should eat with me!
Oh, I'm sorry but I have to leave due to personal reasons.
Without even eating? You should eat a little before going!
I'm sorry! Next time!
Really, I wanted to receive some advice about her job while eating.
I'm busy too.
- What could be the reason?
- What?
The reason for suddenly quitting.
Ah. your secretary. The secretary.
There was nothing I didn't know until now. But with this, there's no way of knowing.
I'm so frustrated that it makes me dizzy.
Is that so?
When your blood sugar is low, red ginseng jelly is the best!
Do you want one?
Are you telling me to eat a bundle of sugar that contains probably around 0.03% of red ginseng?
Never mind, tell me.
Why did Secretary Kim do that?
Oh, I really don't know.
She has worked for you for nine years. That's a long time to endure.
With a woman like that, in the east we call her Bodhisattva and in the west they call her a saint—
What did I just say?
Nine years?
Ni-ni-nine years?
The time has come.
I think it's right when they say it comes in 3, 6, or 9.
3, 6 , or 9?
A rough patch in the relationship.
You know that the love my wife and I share was so destined to be that I married her within the month we met, right?
I know that well. And for your 10th anniversary, instead of gifts you guys exchanged divorce papers.
You just now, you were bad. You were really bad.
At first, we were really! We were really—
passionate.
But, the words that were shared on our third anniversary were,
Honey, I love you.
Why do you think I fell in love with a man like you?
During our sixth wedding anniversary—
Waiter.
Sorry, just looking at the back of your head makes me want to beat you.
And during the ninth anniversary of our wedding—
Even the air you breathe seems to be wasteful, so stop breathing, you bastard!
No way.
By any chance, are you crying?
Can I cry?
No.
If I look back,
whenever 3, 6, or 9 came, we were in a standoff.
Like a bruised apple.
A bruised apple?
Look here.
You can eat around the bruised part, but you get lazy
so you pick out another fresh-looking fruit.
And eat that first.
But if you leave the bruised apple, with the other apples. What will happen?
Then even all the other apples, get bruised too!
All of them get bruised and rot away.
What-- What are you even trying to say?
Before the bruise digs deeper and rots more, find a breakthrough via communication.
A breakthrough, you say...
That's easy.
If you need advice on reaching a breakthrough, come find me.
You divorced her because you couldn't find that breakthrough.
That's right.
This is the payment for the loan. This is the last one, right?
Yes.
Is your name Secretary Kim?
Oh no. No.
Kim Mi So.
Here.
Yes.
Yes, Vice Chairman.
Right now?
Me too?
- We'll be going to his residence now.
- Yes.
You spoke as if you were going back home alone, but why are we going together all of a sudden?
A breakthrough, huh?
Yes?
I'm not someone who gives second chances.
- Yes, of course.
- But to Secretary Kim, specially, I want to give one more chance.
- What?
- This opportunity won't come again, so you should be thankful.
I'll promote you to a director position!
- Ah, that's not it.
- If you have too much work, I'll hire another secretary under you. And the company will cover the costs.
If you want, I can even buy you a house with my own personal funds.
Did you take of all the debts you have at home? I'll even take care of those debts.
Then, from now on, work to the best of your ability.
- Vice Chairman.
- I can promise you.
Wherever you go, you won't be able to find this sort of treatment. And also!
Wherever you go, you won't be able to serve under such a perfect boss.
Even if you jump at this opportunity, I won't call you superficial. So just accept it and keep working.
- But the thing is--
- Yeong Joon!
Secretary Kim, you came?
Right. Right. My dear.
- Please go in.
- Okay, let's go in.
I told you to come more frequently.
Even if we're in the same building, it's so hard to see your face.
I was a bit busy because of the Executive Director Jo incident.
Executive Director Jo was an asset. Did you really have to go that far with him?
It only takes one moment for a company's image to crumble.
Since you trrusted me and left it in my hands, please let me handle it.
You're right, you're right. You're doing great, Yeong Joon.
Honey, of course, Yeong Joon will take care of everything.
You're right, I was being careless.
Oh, sorry.
Did you two also have this period of time: a state of ennui.
A state of ennui?
How did we ever feel disconnected?
As we converse, it's all solved.
There's no one like the chairman.
Let's eat.
Secretary Kim, eat a lot.
Hasn't Yeong Joon gotten more handsome recently?
Not really, it's all because of you, Mother.
It's the reason why I respect you, Mother.
Recently, the Bio Business has been approved by the US FDA and we're working on acquiring the global airline.
Father?
You seem to have something to say judging by your awkward fake cough.
Are you really not planning on getting married?
Yes.
I really-- I, why am I like this?
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
I don't think I'll be able to go on for long.
I saw your health exam results. You seem to be very healthy.
How do they know anything?! I know my body the best!
Before dying, your father wants to see grandchildren for once!
I don't look for any prerequisites in my daughter-in-law.
I heard Secretary Kim quit!
There is no way. I won't let her.
The weather is really nice.
About Yeong Joon...
I heard that he does bring women to social gatherings here and there,
but it doesn't last long.
I don't think he's sincerely meeting them. He says he's only doing it to show others.
Is that really the case?
Yes, I think so.
I heard that he won't even let women touch him. Is that true?
Yes.
So, our Yeong Joon...
perhaps...
is he ga- ga- ga-...
ga- ga- ga- ga-...
Gay?
Oh, it's not anything like that!
Really?
Of course. I've been by his side for a long time, so I know better than anyone.
I'm so relieved.
To be honest, even if the chairman and I couldn't say anything, we were very worried.
Since Yeong Joon is very wary of women other than you.
I was thinking that maybe the rumors were true.
When it comes to Yeong Joon,
how do you think women view him?
It's the best of course. Ability, charm, personality.
Without anything missing, a perfect person.
Isn't that right? You definitely know how to discern people, Secretary Kim!
I would be so happy if someone married our Yeong Joon.
For example, someone like you.
Just a joke.
If there was someone like Secretary Kim out there, I'd immediately send Yeong Joon her way.
Just joking, a joke.
Secretary Kim, you should leave.
Yes.
Then, Madam, I will leave.
Did my mother make you uncomfortable?
Yes, but
I think she was somehow trying to tie you and me together.
So, were you expecting something like that to happen?
No.
It gave me an even clearer conviction on why I should quit soon so we don't receive any further misunderstandings.
What?
I thought that conversation ended earlier. You should know that was an incredible offer!
Yes.
Of course, I know the offer you gave was incredible, but I still want to quit.
Sorry. I can't yield for this.
Don't trigger my competitiveness.
Let me do it.
It's an occupational hazard. I have an obsession in setting everything.
Mi So, let's eat together now.
Unnis*, help yourselves as well.
(elder sisters)
But, my unnis' faces don't look good. Is hospital work too harsh?
Mi So, from now on, don't worry about us.
Your unni couldn't take care of her dongsaengs.
Because of me being ambitious, you had to suffer a lot.
What suffering! You also helped to clear the debts midway.
And you two didn't cause a problem like Dad at least.
A problem?
Dad cause a problem again?
To be honest, in the beginning of this year I found out about his loan shark debts.
- Around three million won?
- What three million?
Why are you telling us only now, Mi So?
You would've been worried if I had told you earlier.
So how did it go?
I solved it by selling my car.
You had a car?
Our Vice Chairman bought it for me because I missed the bus and was late to work for 10 minutes.
I sold it after using it for one week.
I feel so relieved now, after clearing our debts.
Your laughing face is bothering me a lot.
I think it's funny.
Exactly what is funny?
As I think about it now, it's not really funny.
She had been working with me for a long time.
How can she be so relaxed like that?
Didn't you say you met her every day just for work?
What is the reason (for her to quit)?
Do you think Secretary Mi So acted that way to receive an incredible offer?
Think about it carefully. Something might have triggered her to quit on that day.
That day...
Aura!
Ack-cent.
I want to resign now.
Oppa Yeong Joon.
Oh Ji Ran?
I'm going crazy.
You should take your allergy medicine.
Why are you the only one in our family with pollen allergy?
Thanks, Unni.
It was worth me supporting you guys through school.
We don't have any right to face you.
Sorry. It's burnt.
Why do you touch flowers when you have pollen allergy?
Your Vice Chairman ordered you again?
Oppa Yeong Joon!
Why are you here?
I got invited as a celebrity. I saw your name on the invitation list,
so I came here secretly to surprise you.
You should have called me. You came with Secretary Kim because you thought I might be busy, right?
But, Oppa, do I look different somewhere?
The necklace suits you.
This is from you, Oppa.
And, what day is today?
My birthday!
Ji Ran just needs some flowers.
- Give me some flowers.
- What type of flowers do you want?
Flowers. Flower bouquet. A big one.
Thank you, Oppa. You're the best indeed.
They are so pretty.
You are saying Secretary Kim cried?
I thought I was mistaken then.
Secretary Kim's eyes were wet.
Her eyes were moist?
Then, she may think "do I need to buy a bouquet for another girl?"
"That's too dirty. I can't continue working anymore."  Did she  say anything?
No, no. That's not the reason.
I think I know it now. The reason Secretary Kim resigned.
I have a bad feeling towards what you're suspecting.
Why didn't I know about that?
Yeong Joon, this fellow.
Yeong Joon, this fellow?
What exactly  is it?
That personal reason, that unspeakable reason, her eyes.
- Secretary Kim.
Secretary Kim
likes me.
Like me? Nonsense.
No, but why not? Didn't he give you a bunch of clothes and shoes as gifts?
Even if it's so that you look your part, isn't that going a bit overboard?
Vice Chairman likes you. That's confirmed.
No way. Never.
He loves himself too much, to the point that he can't even be satisfied with others.
Liking someone else? Falling in love? Not even once.
- Does that make sense?
-  I said it's true.
Never loved anyone at that age?
He has his secretary.
- Do you want to eat this?
- Eat it, Unni.
I was very careful to prevent her from falling for me.
How considerate you are.
Indeed, if Secretary Kim doesn't have feelings for me after being together for 9 years, she's not a human being but a robot.
Don't be so sure about that.
Secretary Kim, really. We are just working partners.
Yes, that's the reason. She likes me, indeed.
Why does it matter if I like him or hate him?
Vice Chairman and I aren't like that. We just work together.
Also, I just quit working at the company.
- You quit?
- Why did you quit out of the blue?
Did the Vice Chairman pick on you? Oh, that bastard!
No, it's not like that. Now both Father and Unnis have settled down.
And we've paid off our debt. That's why I wanted to quit.
What are you going to do now that you quit?
I still don't know.
It is a pity somehow, because at my age and with my skill-set, it will be hard to find similar benefits.
But, I'm too busy. Plus, if I don't leave now, I feel like I'll never be able to leave.
And also--
Vice Chairman
It's the vice chairman, isn't it?
- Don't answer it.
- Don't answer it. You, don't answer it.
- Don't answer it!
- I said don't answer it!
Yes, Vice Chairman.
You know where I'm at, right? Head over immediately.
Vice Chairman, I have some work to do at the moment. For today only, could you ask Secretary Yang,
or how about I send over a designated driver?
How can I trust them?
Is he telling you to come over now? Hey, give the phone to me.
Oh, then call Ji Ran! For today only, you could sleep with Ji Ran--
Head over immediately.
Vice Chairman? Hello?
Is he telling you to come over now? To come over and drive?
Even if he stays the night out today, there's no one that would say anything.
But I don't know why he's so obsessed with going back to his own house.
That's what I'm saying. It's a relief that you're quitting! A relief!
Where was that key again?
Mi So, I'll take care of it!
Hurry and kill it! Kill it!
It's dead! It's dead!
Mi So, are you okay?
Do you still have a phobia of spiders?
Unni, did I really not get lost when I was young once?
Around when I was four or five?
You're saying stuff like that again. Even when that never happened.
Liking me to that extent,
of course she was upset that I made her buy flowers for another woman.
Secretary Kim, I'll break up with Oh Ji Ran. That will do, right?
Yeong Joon, you were incredibly sharp this time around!
What is he doing? Is Yeong Joon talking to Yeong Joon?
Vice Chairman, I have come.
You cry again and you make someone embarrassed again. Do you like it that much?
I'm sorry.
Throw it away.
Sorry, and also, I will put these flowers in the trunk.
Was it that moving?  Anyway, I can't stop myself.
Sorry.
Who were you with?
It's a secret.
I will end with Oh Ji Ran. That will do, right?
Do you have other woman now?
I won't meet someone else for a while. That will do, right?
Why do you keep asking me if that will do?
I didn't sleep with her. It's satisfying, right?
- What?
- I said I didn't sleep with Oh Ji Ran.
We have a business relationship, Secretary Kim. You know that too.
Yes, of course, I know well.
How much you suffered all this time... I understand it a little.
So, tomorrow rest the whole day and think about it again. It's a special holiday for you.
Really?
But I have an interview for my substitute tomorrow.
Just come for the interview.
Yes. Thank you.
After you quit, did you find a place to go to?
Not yet.
Are you going to stay in Seoul?
I'm still not sure about that.
If you don't have any basic plan, then why did you quit?
I want to now find my life.
What does that mean?
No one's secretary, no one's family member, just the life of Kim Mi So.
Then the time she spent with me, was it not her life?
Pimple??
How dare you came out on my impeccable forehead.
How long has it been since I last slept in?
This is so nice.
I should wake up.
Vice Chairman Lee Yeong Joon's Daily Log
I slept too much.
Who did this investment contract, you yourself?  Thanks.
Hello.
I need a change of pace.
Resignation letter
Kim Mi So
How long has it been since I went to work during the day?
It's so nice.
Hello?
Ji Eun, what should we eat for dinner?
It's me, who else? Secre--, no, Kim Mi So.
You didn't erase my number, did you?
What's with you? Yesterday you said that's just a lump of sugar with 0.03% of red ginseng.
What kind of bullcrap does she mean by trying to find her life?
With the standard 8-hour workday, over 9 years is 18,000 hours.
Secretary Kim didn't take weekends and holidays off over 9 years,
then it's a total of 59,130 hours.
The time she spent with me is more than most couples, so how can she say it has no meaning?
She said it has no meaning? Pity.
Did she get hurt because she liked me so much?
Even though Secretary Kim did her job really well and you feel comfortable with her, still you seem to pay too much attention.
- Could it be... that you like Secretary Kim?
- Have you lost your marbles?
Then why are you worried to this extent?
Other than Secretary Kim, you never let any girl touch you.
Truthfully, there's an abundance of girls around you.
I've never seen you do skinship before.
Do you have trauma with women?
I just hate women.
- Secretary Kim?
- Secretary Kim is different though.
She's a woman. What's different?
Secretary Kim is just
Kim Mi So.
Never mind. I'm leaving.
What is he saying?
Here is the weekly report.
Are you just going to drink it? Should I heat it up for you?
No, it's okay.
You have to heat it up. It'll be better for your health.
It's fine, I'll just eat it.
Well, I said you have to take it warm, give it to--
Sorry. I just wanted to heat it up.
Even though you didn't get to heat up the red ginseng, you sure heat up my insides (meaning made me angry).
Perhaps, Secretary Seol, do you not have thoughts of quitting?
No. I will always be by your side.
Always?
- Leave.
- Yes.
Do you know the secretary guidelines?
You have to be closemouthed but fast on your feet.
Since even I did it without experience or qualifications.
Think coolly. Feel warmly. Run like your feet are on fire.
You will do a good job.
And the last thing I wish to tell the secretary taking over for me,
the reason I am quitting, and more than anything, the most important thing is...
Vice Chairman.
You don't look so good. Are you not feeling well?
I couldn't sleep. Secretary Kim, you look fine though.
I slept a lot thanks to you.
Did you get a pimple on your forehead?
- Should I call dermatologist Dr. Yoon?
- It's fine.
Or should I get a prescription from Dr. Jeon for a sleeping pill?
Are you worried about me right now?
What? Of course I'm worried.
Then are you Secretary Kim or Kim Mi So?
What do you mean?
Vice Chairman, the replacement for Secretary Kim is here for her interview. Should I let her in now?
Tell her to come in now. Secretary Kim, join as well, since she is your replacement.
Yes.
Vice Chairman, I pulled together some questions.
Kim Ji Ah, if you become Secretary Kim, how would you be called?
Secretary Kim or Kim Ji Ah.
I will go by Secretary Kim Ji Ah.
It's Kim Ji Ah, and not Secretary Kim.
Secretary Kim, ask questions as well.
Yes.
Could you speak on the duties of a secretary?
Having the mindset of caring for your boss as you would for a child—
What do you think it would be like working for a boss that was 100% perfect?
Oh, my heart would race.
Do you think you could 100% match a boss that's 100% perfect. Do you think you could satisfy that person?
That must be quite difficult.
Can you take the responsibility not to quit your job with an excuse
as abstract as personal reasons?
I will totally bury my bones here (meaning I will work until I die).
While you work, you may actually bury your bones (meaning you may die with overload of work).
What? It's that hard?
The compensation for your efforts is the best in the nation.
You'll definitely be compensated, but your identity as Kim Ji Ah will be erased. You'll just remain as Secretary Kim.
Then has the time you've been working not been a part of your life, Kim Mi So?
If you pick me, I'll do my best!
You pass!
- Really?
- Assistant Manager Park.
- Yes.
- Show Secretary Kim Ji Ah around. She'll be the new Secretary Kim.
Secretary Kim, take charge and make Secretary Kim an exact copy of you. Then leave.
Yes.
Thank you.
Wait. "You'll find your own life." Exactly what does that mean?
Since I've only lived my life working until now, I want to make time for myself.
And?
And  I'm already 29.
I should date and get married.
What?
I was like that.
What's the occasion? Secretary Kim comes out to gatherings?
Sorry. From now on, don't meet up without me. I now have a lot of time.
You were on the news too, right next to the vice chairman.
You were so cool.
Right. Mi So you were the one that studied the hardest out of all of us.
A total career woman. I'm totally jealous. I'm just an ahjumma.
I'm so tired of looking after the kids!
At least you're the traditional housewife! Look at me. I'm working while looking after my kid.
Mi So, don't get married.
Yeah, definitely don't!
- Why?
- If you get married, you have these kinds of stories.
Right?
I'm going to the restroom.
Oh, my bad.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
What is this? A man's handkerchief, necktie, and lighter?
Whose bag is this?
It's mine. You never know when the Vice Chairman may need those.
A career woman lives like this.
Let's get on!
Let's sit here.
Your babies are so small.
Alright.
Yeah.
Is your name Secretary Kim?
Oh no, Kim Mi So.
Secretary Kim
Kim Mi So.
Here.
Taking Over the New Occupation Manual
The most important thing
is to make sure to have time for yourself.
Your predecessor, Kim Mi So.
Taking Over the New Occupation Manual
It's all done.
One's own time? Life? Dating? Marriage?
How could she say things like that to me, as if I were a stranger?
Who?
- How am I?
- What?
How am I?
What's new? Of course, you're  the perfect man.
Capable, good looking, tall, well-mannered.
And, sexy.
But why did Secretary Kim do that?
What? What did Secretary Kim do?
Are you talking about another girl in front of me?
Kim Mi So
To my brother
Who is this?
Vice Chairman, why are you here at this time?
First, please come in.
Don't order me around. I'll talk outside.
Sure.
Dating and marriage, were you being serious?
Did you come all the way here at this time just to ask about that?
Why, so suddenly? Was there a person you met without me knowing?
Vice Chairman, are you angry?
No, it doesn't matter to me who you meet. Why would I be angry?
That's what I'm saying.
Just answer the questions I'm asking.
I don't have someone I'm meeting secretly.
Of course it had to be that.
- What?
There's no reason for me to meet with someone else without you knowing. And did I even have the time to do so?
I always got to work at 6 AM, and I didn't know when I'd get off.
When you call me, even when I'm sleeping, I'll get right up and head to you.
So? You're having a hard time convincing me.
If I continue to keep working by your side,
I can't get married, I feel like I'll get older.
Only... for that reason?
'Only... for that reason?'
When I get older and can't stay by your side any longer, who will take care of me when I'm jobless?
Alright. I promise you'll have your job for your entire lifetime.
I dislike that even more.
You're telling me to stay by your side and get lonelier as I age.
So, to get married, you have to quit the company?
Yes.
You want to get married that bad?
Then keep doing your work.
I, Lee Yeong Joon, will let you marry me.
Timing and Subtitles brought by The Perfect Secretaries Team @ Viki
♬ Between you and me, between the two of us, like a scent ♬
♬ this feeling spreads everywhere ♬
♬ It makes my heart beat, it makes me dizzy ♬
♬ Is this what they call love ♬
♬ My days are full of only you ♬
♬ It's quite rough ♬
What's Wrong With Secretary Kim
I'm going to date now.
Is trying to keep Secretary Kim on the level of completing a company merger?
Write where you'd want to go with someone you have feelings for.
Who wants to go get pork spareribs?
Yeah! I do, I do!
Our department store's liquor income is our weakness but—
When we're eating, we don't talk about work.
Secretary Kim, when it comes to places like the noraebang —
Then, why don't you just go back?
Okay, I said okay. Why do you have so much to say?
I'm just answering the questions you asked.
Look at this, look at this again. Talking back to me! Secretary Kim.
Yes?
Secretary Kim, happy and romantic days like today, will become your daily lifestyle from now on.
♬ My heart is spreading towards yours ♬