ALL CHARACTERS, INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 1
100 PERCENT PURE CARBONIC ACID
THIS IS THE TASTE OF TRUE BEER
Yes. The story will be published shortly,
at around 7 a.m.
But I said to Despatch, "Interlocking
fingers doesn't mean they're dating.
Ask anyone you see on the streets."
And if you look closely,
they aren't interlocked.
You're holding his wrist.
So I said, "They're obviously not dating."
I strongly denied it,
and we concluded that you two
are good friends who like to pull pranks.
You call that a prank?
Yes. I told them you two are very close
and that's how you usually fool around...
I mean, that's how
you two usually hang out.
THOSE TWO ARE DEFINITELY DATING
Right.
We were close.
Although it's all over now.
PLEASE LET ME JUST GO HOME
All right.
It already happened, so it's fine.
It's all good,
but can you do something
about the blur effect?
Should I tell them to blur your face more?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
They blurred my earrings too.
It's the accessory item I'm promoting
the hardest out of the whole collection.
The blur effect should be...
How shall I put this?
Can they carefully shrink it
so that the earrings show right away?
Actually, a full shot would be better.
That way, people can see my purse
-and shoes too.
-Got it.
Purchasing Manager.
What should you do, then?
-Pardon me?
-The earrings, purse, and shoes.
You need to secure enough stock.
Orders will pile up
when they start trending.
Okay.
Who is she? What's with all this fuss?
Isn't that her? The woman
who's supposedly dating actor Cha Sang-u?
You're right. Does she think
she's a celebrity? Why bring bodyguards?
She's not even that pretty.
-He deserves better.
-I bet it's her money.
I feel like I'm getting way more attention
than I usually do.
Why did you hire these bodyguards?
Oh, in case Cha Sang-u's angry fans
may attack you...
"Angry fans"?
Why? I'm the one who should be angry,
not them.
Ms. Yoon, please calm down.
We did half of our yearly revenue
in just one day.
The stock price is going up too.
Look at you. Are you a celebrity or what?
Who's this?
Your eldest brother!
She doesn't even have
her brother's number? That rude stuck-up.
Why did you call?
Hey. Last time, it was a baseball player.
-A soccer player.
-I mean, a soccer player.
And this time, it's an idol singer?
-No, an actor.
-It's an actor?
So? Is that why you called?
You probably don't care to know
what's going on
with our family because
you're too busy embarrassing us,
but didn't you see the news?
Dad's being released on probation today.
I don't care whether or not
you visit us on the holidays
or for the memorial ceremonies,
-but shouldn't you come by today?
-Is this your number?
Yes, it is.
Can you save it, for heaven's sake?
Don't change your number.
It'd be a hassle
to have to block it twice.
BLOCK NUMBER
-Damn it.
-Did she hang up on you again?
-This little brat.
-Just leave her be.
It's been years since Se-ri estranged
the whole family. Don't bother.
I only called her
because Dad wanted me to.
By the way, why did Father
summon all of us today?
That must be it, right?
-Announcing the heir.
Chairman Yoon Jeung-pyeong
of Queens Group,
who was arrested in March
for violating the Act on
Aggravated Punishment
of Economic Crimes, has been released
on probation after 283 days.
Chairman Yoon has announced
that he will be stepping down,
so all eyes are on who,
between his eldest son, Yoon Se-jun,
and his second eldest son, Yoon Se-hyeong,
will end up taking over
the leadership of the group.
-Sir.
-Here he comes.
-Please say a few words.
-A comment, please.
-Please tell us!
-Just a comment, please!
What is this?
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR RELEASE
Father, I made this tofu cake
to congratulate you on your release.
My wife is the best.
-Congratulations, Dad.
-Congratulations!
You seem to be in a great mood today.
I'm so happy
that Father is finally out of jail.
People are only interested
in the power dynamics among the siblings
and who will end up
inheriting the company.
I mean, what's wrong with people?
I guess they think rich people like us
don't even have families.
We're so close, you know.
Right, Sang-a?
Yes, of course.
Oh, right. Se-jun, you had a fistfight
with the labor union leader.
Has it all been sorted out?
They're in the process of
reaching a settlement, peacefully.
It can happen when two guys
are trying to talk things out.
Exactly, it happens.
By the way, Sang-a,
I heard Se-hyeong got duped
by an investment scam.
When?
What can you do about the stock price
plunging 50 percent?
But the fact that people are questioning
your leadership skills and qualifications
makes me so angry.
Just because you fell victim
to a high-value fraud, people call you
an idiot and treat you like a retard.
Who's calling my brother an idiot?
-I heard--
-It's not a fraud.
I just can't get a hold of my friend
at the moment. That's all.
Take care of it,
or all the shareholders will sue you.
Mind your own business.
Dad, Se-jun beat up the union leader
and broke his tooth.
I promised him
that I'll pay for his dental implant.
-Are you boasting?
-You think I am, retard?
-What? You prick.
-How dare you call me a prick!
-Where is Se-ri?
-You...
Did you not get the message
that I wanted Se-ri here today?
I tried getting in touch with her
many times,
but it looks like that brat
blocked my number.
Dad, congratulations
on getting out on probation.
I heard you wanted me to be here today.
Is there something you'd like to say?
You should
move back in.
Is that it?
I was wondering why.
You look great.
Look after your health.
I came and said hi, so I'll get going.
I want you to take over my position.
-Dad.
-Father.
Honey.
Listen.
You left home and started your own company
ten years ago.
I've definitely seen what you can do.
So,
I want you to run the company in my place.
-Okay, I'll do that.
-Hey.
-You brat, you don't know anything!
-That's right!
If I'm your successor, will I have
the authority to appoint new CEOs
for our subsidiaries?
Of course, you will.
That's great.
I always thought that a few of the CEOs
are underqualified.
For instance, those who tend
to clash with their employees
and those who often get sued
or have caused the company great damage
due to their own ignorance.
We should fire such CEOs
without any hesitation.
I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.
Give me some time though.
My company recently launched
an extreme-sports apparel line,
so it's grown even bigger.
I'll look for
a good management specialist.
All right.
Can you meet me in my office tomorrow?
Tomorrow, I can't.
We're doing the final test
on an important new product.
Then,
I plan to announce it at the upcoming
general shareholders' meeting,
so let's meet before that.
Okay.
Then enjoy your dinner, everyone.
You might get indigestion if I stay.
I'm leaving.
Ms. Yoon, when did you learn paragliding?
Did I not tell you?
I got my certification in Interlaken
when I went to Switzerland.
Oh, I see. We could've tested it
and just submitted
a report to you.
You didn't have to do this yourself.
It looks like I'll get quite busy.
I'm in a rush
because I need to climb someplace.
"Climb"? Where?
High up.
You're already in a high place.
So you mean, even higher?
As early as tomorrow morning,
you'll see my name all over the news.
Don't be too surprised.
Will it be another dating scandal?
No.
All right. Shall we get started?
The wind is quite strong though.
We've checked the weather forecast,
but will you be all right?
Mr. Hong.
Why does the wind blow?
Well, I'm not sure.
It's blowing to move on,
not to stay.
The wind needs to keep moving
for me to fly.
Ms. Yoon, please be careful!
You're doing a great job, seriously.
You've been working so hard, Se-ri.
Now, I can just soar high up.
This is nice.
Look at the beautiful color of the forest
and the lush green fields.
I haven't seen a scenery like this
in so long.
My gosh.
Look, that tractor is flying in the wind.
Why is that happening?
My gosh.
KOREAN DEMILITARIZED ZONE
NORTHERN LIMIT LINE 1,000M
FOR PEACE, PROSPERITY, AND UNIFICATION
OF KOREAN PENINSULA
Captain Ri.
They're headed in this direction,
judging from the sound of the gunshots.
Maybe it's a deserter from the South.
The combat site is 400m away
from our current location.
Going in at eleven o'clock.
Total count, ten.
K2 automatic rifle, six in total.
And Tokarev TT-33. Three are in use.
-TT-33?
-They're our comrades.
Step back.
Take one more step,
and you'll be entering our garrison.
GARRISON: MILITARY POST
Hand these three over, and we'll back off.
-They're our comrades.
-Captain.
We got the State Security Department's
approval and came here to hunt deers.
We just got lost because of the tornado.
They crossed the Southern Limit Line
and got caught
while digging up cultural artifacts.
Can you prove it?
This shows screenshots
from our thermal camera footage.
Is anyone injured?
-No.
-We've gauged the situation,
so let's drop our weapons.
I swear on my country's honor
that we will strictly punish them.
When it comes to punishment,
we, the North, certainly outdo the South.
We'll drop our weapons
on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
MILITARY POLICE
Alpha One.
Just return. Don't get into conflict.
-Don't get into conflict with the North.
-Thunderbolt One.
Do you hear me?
No conflict with the South.
Return at once.
Greetings, sir.
Company Five is on standby
to transfer the grave robbers,
whom we arrested
while patrolling the demilitarized zone.
Company Five Captain Ri Jeong Hyeok.
Good work.
Anything else?
Because of the tornado earlier in the day,
a lot of the barbed-wire fences
fell down along with the trees.
The high-voltage transformer for
the electric fence isn't working either.
We should tighten security
for the areas with the damages
until everything is fixed.
Yes, we should.
Is it tomorrow? The company switch.
Yes, sir.
What a shame.
All of this happened on your last day.
From the tornado to the grave robbers.
That's okay, sir.
They probably crossed
the Southern Limit Line
due to a misunderstanding.
Let's be lenient.
It happened inside our patrol zone.
It cannot be taken lightly.
You're well aware of the fact
that the State Security Department
issued them the pass
to enter the demilitarized zone.
Nothing good will come out of this
being brought up at the final assessment.
So the State Security Department
gave those grave robbers permission
to cross the Southern Limit Line
and steal artifacts.
Is that what you're saying?
Of course not, Captain Ri.
I promised the captain from the South
that we will investigate this matter.
I wish to keep that promise.
All right. Go ahead
and keep your promise, then.
But can I make a promise too, Captain Ri?
I, Jo Cheol Gang, never go easy on anyone
no matter what their ranks are.
If you commit any act
that may threaten our army's security
and get caught by me,
you will be finished on the spot.
Of course,
you'll never do anything like that.
But they say
that a thing or a person
is bound to change all the time.
Isn't that how life is, after all?
Gosh, don't even get me started.
If he gets that cocky
with a State Security Department officer,
what's going to happen to us?
I guess he'll look all cool and tough,
but the State Security Department
will keep a close watch on us
from now on because of it.
That's what I'm trying to say.
By the way, how did Captain Ri
end up at the outpost line?
He's from Pyongyang,
so he probably has a high status.
Why not just enjoy
a comfortable life there?
That's why they say
you've got to watch out for the rich.
From front to back,
they want everything under their control
so that they can forever win
General Kim's love.
-I see.
-All right.
Just know that this wine is from 1953,
which was before the armistice was signed.
-Oh, my.
-All right.
Just one glass of this 60-year-old
snake wine
can make even those suffering
from malnutrition jump around with vigor.
-This is medicine, not wine.
-Medicine.
Then I'd love a glass of this medicine.
Sure thing.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Enjoy. All right, you're next.
But is it okay to drink like this
while on duty?
Hey, we worked day and night
for two months straight.
The company switch will happen
in the morning,
so it will be fine.
-You cannot go in.
-Please.
My boss...
My boss is a lady.
Gosh, excuse me. Wait!
My gosh.
119 RESCUE SERVICES
Please calm down.
-Sir, you must keep out.
-Let go!
Wait!
Excuse me! Hey.
-Where's my boss?
-I don't know.
Didn't you record anything?
Where's the camera?
-In that situation? I couldn't.
-What did you do, then?
I nearly died!
-Okay, but where is Ms. Yoon?
-I'm going to sue you people!
What are you talking about?
Wait. Gosh, this is nuts.
How unprofessional.
I told her we could just submit
a report to her.
Why did she suddenly want
to do this herself? This is crazy.
She talked about
going high up or something.
How far have you gone, Ms. Yoon?
What?
Did I faint?
Gosh.
Where am I?
It hurts.
What is this place?
This is Se-ri. Answer me, Mr. Hong.
Hello?
What the hell?
Where am I?
Am I at a national park or what?
Gosh! My goodness.
This is too high.
Hello?
Hello? Anybody around?
Help! Anybody around?
Didn't you hear something just now?
Pardon? I didn't hear anything, sir.
A woman's voice.
It sounded like she was crying.
Stop it. You're scaring me.
This is Owl. Pigeon, answer.
This is Pigeon. What's the matter?
You'll have to come here.
The tornado damaged
all the barricades and sand plates.
Okay.
-Captain Ri.
-You go ahead.
I'll look around this area.
Yes, sir.
Here! Someone's here!
You're a soldier.
Is the army nearby dispatched to find me?
-Password.
-What?
What is that?
Don't come near. Talk to me from there.
Talk to me from there.
Come down.
I wish I could go down,
but as you can see, it's so high up here.
And I don't have any energy left.
Oh, my. I'm coming down.
I'm unbuckling now.
State your occupation and name.
Well, I work for a fashion company.
I don't think you will know its name.
And I don't feel comfortable telling you
my name because we just met.
And...
You made a tough decision.
Welcome to the Republic of Korea.
"Republic of Korea"?
What was it called?
Defector. You're a defector
from North Korea, right?
Maybe you're not.
An armed communist...
Or a spy?
Are you
a North Korean elite
urgently dispatched
in order to carry out a special mission?
Whatever you are, don't worry.
I will not report you or anything.
I don't mind others' business at all.
I'm busy with my own business.
-Now if you'll excuse me.
-Halt.
I halted. Look. I'm standing still.
Listen.
Could you just let me go home?
-Where do you live?
-Seoul, Gangnam-gu, Cheong...
I can't give you any further details.
It's a long way.
I will find my way.
Thanks for your concern.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I didn't come to the South.
-Pardon?
-You came to the North.
North? North Korea?
Come on. Don't be ridiculous.
How is this place...
Seriously?
Come on. Stop kidding me.
No way.
We're at the demilitarized zone,
the 38th parallel.
-It's the Northern Limit Line.
-"Demilitarized zone"?
The place where the film
Joint Security Area was set in?
Then this is not completely North Korea.
It's the territory of
the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.
And an unidentified South Korean
trespassed on the land.
-You'll go through legal procedures--
-Wait.
I didn't trespass. Look over there.
I was paragliding.
The weather was all sunny and great.
But then suddenly it went crazy
and a tornado came,
which wasn't even on the weathercast.
Tractors and pigs were
all flying around
and the flood carried away people.
I was carried away by the wind too.
Then I passed out.
And I found myself here.
So what I'm saying is, it was an accident.
It couldn't be helped.
Okay.
Thank you. You understand.
Explain like that
when you are investigated.
What? Why would I be investigated?
According to the law of the republic,
voluntary enterers must be tied up
and investigated.
Tied up? You will tie me up?
You flew over
on an unpowered flying vehicle.
We can't send you back
without any investigation.
Then what if they frame me
as a beautiful spy
or a beautiful secret agent,
torture me, and send me
to places like Aoji Coal Mine?
Then what do I do?
That won't happen.
-Are you sure?
-I can't say I'm sure.
Then how am I supposed to trust you?
Would you if you were me?
Whether you trust me or not
is not my business.
Come on.
Don't be so irresponsible.
I think it won't take long if I run.
Please just let me go. Please.
I'm a really good runner.
I will be gone in no time.
-I won't cause any harm to you.
-Halt.
If you turn a blind eye to this,
you're saving a person's life.
Wait. That's a minefield.
Mine?
Where?
There are many lost mines there.
They were carried away by the heavy rain
and buried out of sight.
I'm an expert in that area.
Do you think you can get out
without my help?
I get it, but could you just stay there?
Why does he keep approaching?
If you don't listen to me and move,
you might lose your ankle...
-What's the matter?
-I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
I said I'm fine.
I think you stepped on a lost mine.
-No, I didn't.
-You didn't?
Are you sure?
Are you sure you don't need my help?
Then try moving and turning around.
You can't move.
This is Mountain Hawk. This is Mountain...
This is Pigeon. Answer, Mountain Hawk
Thank you.
Don't thank me. I'm not giving it to you.
Don't forget that I have a gun in my hand.
Don't forget that if you shoot me,
you're losing the only person
who can help you.
By the way, I don't have
much knowledge in that area.
Do experts sometimes step on mines too?
If you keep standing like that,
your feet will go numb.
-I'm okay.
-Okay.
You keep saying you're okay,
so I'll just head off.
I have a lot of things to do. Well, then.
Fine.
Leave that at least.
It will soon drift down to you.
I need some time to escape too.
You understand me, right?
I'm in huge trouble myself,
so I don't have the time
to worry about others.
Bye.
Don't shoot me from the back.
That's just sneaky.
Do you see the rectangular box
in front of you?
-I do.
-That's a PMD series mine.
Why are there so many mines here?
Try to stay as close to the bank
as possible.
Keep watching your step.
I'm saying this
because we will never meet again.
Your looks are totally my type.
If our countries reunite,
let's meet a different occasion.
How could you
make a joke in this situation?
By the way, which way is the South?
Keep following the path,
then you will meet a forked road.
Then...
go to the right.
Can I trust you?
Stop asking and make a decision.
I already said my answer.
Captain Ri.
Is everything okay?
-Captain Ri.
-I'm here!
Captain Ri.
I've been looking for you.
Tell the troops
to arrest anyone suspicious
found in the area.
Is it a voluntary enterer?
Or is it a spy?
It's a South Korean woman
who came by an accident.
Arrest her without shooting her.
Forward the command.
Yes, sir.
This is Pigeon. Answer, Cuckoo.
Who is looking for Cuckoo?
I sent the command by radio.
Captain Ri.
Is everything okay?
Did you...
Don't worry.
I will call the engineer corps right away.
Why don't you do it,
First Lieutenant Park?
You have disarmed mines, right?
Just once when I was a recruit.
I trust you.
I will do my best, sir.
Wait. Are you going to do it
with bare hands?
You need to remove the safety pin
with this first.
Yes, sir. Don't worry, sir.
Be careful.
If you don't remove the pin correctly,
you might hit the fuse.
Yes, sir.
Be extra careful with that part.
Make sure to do it gently.
Be careful.
You said you trusted me.
I did.
-Is it over?
-Yes, it's over, sir.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
He said I should go right.
I must trust him. There's no other way.
He didn't look like he would lie.
How do I trust him? He's from the North.
This must be a scheme.
A South Korean woman seems to
have stumbled into our area.
We were told to shoot her right away,
so she must be some kind of an armed spy.
-A spy?
-An armed spy?
Gosh. First grave robbers, and now a spy.
All this happened just before
I switch commands. I'm so unlucky.
I'm totally exhausted.
Hey, spread out in pairs.
Yes, sir. Let's go.
Why couldn't she just come tomorrow
after we switch commands?
Then the 6th company would
have taken the job.
Still, if we catch the armed spy,
we will be rewarded well.
Master Sergeant Pyo, you need a promotion.
-A promotion?
-Yes, sir.
Then maybe an infallible marksman,
Pyo Chi Su, should make a move.
-Master Sergeant.
-Yes.
-I think I have to go to the toilet.
-Go ahead.
I was wondering when I will receive
the General's medal.
I guess it's today.
Did I
see it wrong?
There she is.
Hey, stay still. If she was still,
I would've definitely shot her.
That damn woman is freaking fast.
Is she a ghost or what?
This is Cuckoo.
I request backup.
Goodness.
Why are they chasing me?
I thought I was free to go.
MINEFIELD
But that area is packed with mines.
UNCHECKED MINEFIELD
Why is she running over a minefield?
Our fence is over there.
You two.
Follow her along the left clear path.
-I'll take the right path.
-Yes, sir.
That damn woman!
Stop there!
-Damn it.
-Stop there, woman!
Come here!
Hey! Come here!
We will not kill you.
Hey! You! That woman is crazy.
-Why is she going there?
-How did they come here?
No. Don't go.
That's not the way back to your country!
Come back here!
-What?
-That's the wrong way!
-Come back!
-What are they saying?
If you go there, we will all die!
Don't go!
-That's not the right way!
-Don't go!
What an idiot.
Why did she cross that fence?
What do we do, sir?
Radio the guard post first.
This is Cuckoo. Answer, Seagull.
Seagull. Hey! Seagull!
"People in love are meant to meet.
No matter how far you travel,
in the end,
you will come back."
Put that necklace on.
Dear my proud son, Eun Dong.
Are you staying healthy in the army?
Ten years could be a long time
or a short time,
depending on how you think of it.
I wish you finish
your ten years of service safely
and come back home
with a hero's medal on your chest.
Mother.
SE-RI
The person you have called
is not available...
Hello.
Secretary Na.
What?
What are you talking about?
Today,
I want to ask you for intercessory prayer.
My husband and I have
faced an unexpected crisis.
All we did was to be nice,
and this is how it paid off.
That low-class...
someone is
coveting my husband's position.
MY HUSBAND
Since my husband is
the eldest son in the family,
he should...
MY HUSBAND
Please excuse me for a second. I'm sorry.
Honey.
I'm at the prayer meeting.
I'll call you when it's over.
Se-ri is missing.
What?
What? Really?
Okay.
Please keep me updated.
Goodness.
Ms. Do, what's the matter?
You see.
I didn't even start the prayer,
but God has responded already.
-Praise God.
-Hallelujah.
Helicopters, drones, probes, search dogs.
We are using every method we can use
for the search.
-So don't worry.
-Well.
I'm sure you'll take care of it.
What worries us the most is...
the press.
Once the reporters begin
to write articles,
things will get complicated.
-The stock price will drop too.
-Right.
Don't worry about that.
The incident will be reported,
but we will keep
the personal information secret.
In this case, how long is the golden hour?
This is a disaster situation,
so there's no fixed golden hour,
but from my personal experience,
It's about 48 hours.
-That long?
-That's long.
-Excuse me?
-If she is alive,
she should have called us by now.
You said she wasn't
in nearby hospitals either.
It's been already over ten hours.
The chances that she's alive
must be pretty low.
-Right?
-Right.
You have dogs. Bring more dogs.
Look at how big the land is.
At this rate, it will take forever.
-Sir, we're already--
-There's nobody over there.
No one is searching over there.
You said you would leave.
You said you would disown our family.
I guess you want to take
what you can take.
Tell Dad that you can't do it.
Whenever I get startled
or scared, I still say this.
"Mom!"
How funny is that?
Because I don't have a mom.
What kind of mother wants
her daughter to be gone?
Right?
Mom!
See? It's not supposed to get ripped
in this situation.
As soon as I get back,
I will fail this product.
You guys are so dead.
I crossed the fence,
but why is there no one here?
What's going on?
Are all the soldiers on leave or what?
-It's all because of me--
-That's not true.
It's because of me.
Hey.
What's the point in finding whom to blame?
If you put it that way,
Captain Ri is the first one to lose her
because he stepped on a mine,
so he has the responsibility too.
I mean, Captain Ri would never have
intended to step on it either.
Everyone knows
that place is full of lost mines.
Even raw recruits know that.
I'm sure he was being careful enough.
Still, he stepped on it.
What can we do about that?
Master Sergeant Pyo, did you drink?
What?
Well, I didn't drink alcohol.
I just had a glass of medicine.
Again,
there's no point in finding whom to blame.
We must hurry and find that woman.
If that woman gets caught
by the State Security Department,
we will all be dead meat.
"Dead meat"?
We will walk into a prison
and come out dead.
Prison?
A dishonorable discharge
at best.
Mother.
It's time for the company switch.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
Attention.
MY PROUD HOMELAND
Company Five has completed
transferring the task at the guard post.
Captain of Company Five, Ri Jeong Hyeok.
How did that unpowered aircraft reach
our land?
It's precisely because it's unpowered.
Had it been powered,
the radar would have caught it
no matter the wind.
The thermographic camera can't catch
unpowered aircraft,
so you miss it
if you don't spot it with your eyes.
If wind carried her over the border,
-that woman must be panicking.
-Hey!
I am panicking, too!
We will catch her
before the words get out, right?
We must catch her
no matter what.
Why does it feel like I was here before?
I shouldn't wander any longer.
I won't come back here.
Let's not meet again.
Bye.
How is the search going?
You saw how widespread the search is.
That's your problem.
I am not talking about the search
for Yoon Se-ri.
Yoon Se-ri isn't the one
you should be looking for.
What are you talking about?
Stop quizzing me and say what you want.
The position
is open.
It's open right now.
Will you miss your chance again?
This is the last chance.
If you don't want to lose it forever,
find him right away.
The man who ran away with your money,
Gu Seung-jun.
SHENYANG, CHINA
Guard the door.
Let me know if you see someone suspicious.
Yes, sir.
Is he trustworthy?
My goodness.
You know how carefully I choose my people.
He is trustworthy.
How about you, Mr. Oh?
Are you trustworthy?
You should know that I am trustworthy
at this point.
That was exactly what I said
before I backstabbed Yoon Se-hyeong.
You have a point.
You are incredible.
Mr. Yoon must be in a lot of trouble.
He isn't the type to give up so easily.
He must have followed my trail
to the Philippines by now.
To follow my trail here,
it would take four days tops.
Where should I go from here?
That's right.
With enough money and manpower,
you could chase someone to anywhere
in the world.
One place is an exception.
Internet,
Interpol, and phone roaming
are all useless at that place.
So where is that place?
Hurry up and tell me, would you?
INVESTIGATION OFFICE
OF THE CIVILIAN POLICE BATTALION
Sir.
Sit down.
Relax and eat.
We were quite successful this time.
We have some Goryeo celadon pottery
and a gold Buddha statue.
The Buddha statue is
in the best condition.
There is a gold chamber pot too.
Good work.
Where are the goods?
Are you certain?
Of course.
By the way, what will become of us?
Things got out of hand
because of that damned captain.
We won't be deported
to Pyongyang, will we?
Ri Jeong Hyeok is no match of mine.
Prepare to receive your rewards.
Thank you.
Your food will go cold.
Eat.
I NEED A RIDE
What? Open the door!
Open the door!
There are people inside.
My goodness.
Captain.
That woman wouldn't have made it
out of here safely.
She could have gotten eaten by a boar.
There would be no need to notify
the State Security Department.
What do you mean?
Geum Eun Dong is
the head of a big family which comprises
of a single mother and four siblings.
Eun Dong's mother is waiting
for her son to return as a hero.
It's the same for every parent.
Since Kim Ju Meok watched
a South Korean drama during work hours,
he might not be able to make it to...
His father might beat him to death first.
If you commit a crime,
it's natural to receive a punishment.
It applies to Geum Eun Dong
and Kim Ju Meok who left their posts
as well as me
who failed to capture that woman
and you
who drank during work.
Captain.
Here.
Thank goodness.
I am home.
I nearly ended up going to North Korea.
What happened today
deserves an interview with CNN.
I will go to the town,
borrow a phone,
and call a taxi so that I can go home.
I will have Dr. Im come over and receive
physical therapy.
I am almost home.
Why is this place so dark?
Is everyone asleep?
Excuse me. May I borrow your cellphone?
What? Let's go.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Comrade, your briquette didn't go out
during the night, did it?
No, it didn't.
Comrade, have you been well
throughout the night?
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Oh, we have electricity now.
We are only getting it
when the sun is about to go up.
But it's nice to have electricity
before we start to cook breakfast.
That's true.
Why did you come ten minutes late today?
It wasn't intentional, okay?
Give me food waste.
Here you go. Give me chicken egg tickets.
Here are ten chicken egg tickets.
Hurry up and give me the eggs.
You collected a lot.
You are so diligent.
Those people...
What are they doing?
They are still warm.
You are right.
-All right, everyone.
-Mom!
-Here it is.
-Let's get started
with the daily exercise routine.
-Let's go.
-Come on out.
Let's hurry up.
THE GREAT LEADER IS ALWAYS WITH US
-Comrade Rim Jin Ju.
-Here.
-Comrade Jeong Woo Pil.
-Comrade Park Eun Byeol.
-What are they doing?
Comrade Park Eun Byeol isn't here yet.
-She is always late!
-What's with the accent?
We will be late for school
if we wait for her.
Let's go without her.
-Let's go.
Forward march!
-Where are we?
-We reached the town
-Where are we going?
-Going to school
-Why are we going?
-Going to study
-Going with whom?
-We are going together
PARADISE OF PEOPLE
THE GREAT LEADER IS ALWAYS WITH US
-We reached the town
-Where are we going?
-Going to school
-Why are we going?
-Going to study
-Going with whom?
What?
Am I still in North Korea?
Mr. Hong.
Hello. Hello.
You can hear me, right?
I know you can hear me.
Fire the event company.
Did they even check the weather?
How could they be so careless?
Once I go back, I won't let you...
No, no.
I will let you be.
I promise I will let you be.
I am not mad.
You aren't answering
because you think I am mad, right?
I am not mad. I am really okay.
So please answer me.
I think...
I am in some kind of a national park.
I saw an elk earlier.
See if there is a national park nearby.
It might sound like an order,
but it's a request.
Come on.
Don't do this to me.
I have so much work.
I have a mountain of work.
For example,
I was planning
to give the employees a raise
and a big bonus.
Did you hear that?
I bet you did.
You are too embarrassed
to answer me so suddenly, right?
Anyone,
please come to me.
Here!
-I come from a rich family in South Korea.
-I'm not interested.
Won't all of you in huge trouble
if people find out that I'm hiding here?
That means you'll get kicked out.
-I heard you need this job.
-They said she died.
He's in hiding
after the one-billion-won scheme.
I guess there might be a new account.
Why are you here?
His resume doesn't have anything
about family background.
Everything will look suspicious.
-I want to return the favor.
-You don't have to.
There was no favor to begin with.